hello everyone
welcome
um to my presentation on man life
insurance my name is delene Grant and uh
just just just a review here man life
insurance um is a company it's insurance
company for B mobility and um they
represent employees for short-term
disability they actually they they're
not helping us really they're in favor
for Bell okay this compies located in
Montreal Quebec Canada okay thank you
it's all it's it's it's it's um all over
Canada you know but I was dealing with
the one here that was located in Quebec
Canada
okay damages criminal acts my life is
responsible for everything that happened
in my life there after including murder
attempts yes if you already saw my uh um
motor vehicle accidents okay
um just to cover up their deception
because they have been deceiving
changing my medical records and all that
and man new life is very instrumental
too uh because they are guilty guilty in
this start in my medical records okay
this is 2017 and this is part two of two
okay pleasee to pause and read if I'm
going too fast okay thank
you as I may mention in my f the first
part of 2017 the first presentation for
I made mention that I went to Dr James
Chang on May in May okay
um he
recorded
okay right hand still hurting that's it
here and two as you can see he said
right risk is still stolen okay I'll
enlarge
it there it is okay May 15th
okay so in bigr D is saying there was no
more selling and all that you know you
know there he was trying to do me wrong
okay and um I was still at my desk on
May 24th I was I I I got the wsib lawyer
right also oh it was for D it was it was
for the re main reason was that I was
denied um wsp workplace safety insurance
by board WSB right however manual life
manual life insurance decided to seize
my benefits benefits were seized on
April 10th okay benefits seized on April
10th I asked for an extension of
benefits spoke with supervisor and Human
Resources but was denied I had to wait
until January 28th n 2018 9 months right
9 months my right hand was still soen
and pain picture below at my desk using
ice pack from my painful swollen right
hand so I was still working on it and I
was using my left hand Network to do
work
wow I guess slavery days will not have
not been abolished wow please be for to
pause and read thank
you here is the ice pack anyone know
this ice pack with the Igloo on it
showing Igloo I so not um lying okay May
24th thank
you I was forced by Dr James Chang to
see Dr handles men okay I wanted to see
another specialist but Dr James CH said
that um Dr hesman is still my specialist
for the year so I have to return to him
I didn't want to return to Dr hesman
because Dr hesman sent me back to use my
left hand Dr handman did not uh uh
schedule a follow-up uh um appointment
for my injury I was left on my own I
didn't want to go to him but anyway when
I went Dr handers man's office as soon
as I entered the door the opening there
of the door and Dr Anders man looked up
and saw me I'm and God know I'm not
lying we look up and saw me he he looked
Stern he saw me and he's like oh and
then he got up I'm send it back to Sun
book I'm sending back to Sunny book he
was actually storming out of his office
and I had to say hold on Doc please hold
on right and then and then um he said he
said they said I I I okay it's now June
and I don't know the swelling is still
there I need to understand about this um
um I I said I needed to understand about
this injury because I've never heard of
De before you know that's what I needed
I was concerned needed answers and he
stormed out and said I don't know and he
left right how however so when I went
out front I it did not examine me at all
when I went out front I got the
requisition cuz he said he sending me
back he was sending me back to
Sunnybrook so I got the
requisition okay again from the
receptionist so Dr hman in his report I
got this report because of what I had to
do after right and I got this I I it was
um I got a support later on in the year
right it says June 12th and yes I went
to him on June 12th right but his report
is like I he examined me this doctor
this specialist did not examine me at
all this specialist saw my hand because
I asked him why is there still swelling
and pain this is now June and from I saw
him in March and he did not do a
physical exam on me either right I
needed answers then he's saying today on
physical exam comination there slight
puffiness over the dors some of the
right distal forearm oh really this is
and then he said thus at present she may
have a right deck of intis it has never
gone away it has never gone away you
understand I believe he acted this way
because of man life insurance he didn't
want you know he did he did not want to
um get involved so he stormed out all
right in his in this note this is what
um this is anyway he says he said it's
going to send me back to Sunbrook
hospital if there is no inflammation not
warranting an injection or if cortisone
injection is done if it is done right
without sustain um
sematic Improvement if there's no
improvement after the ultrasound after
the injection sorry I would suggest as
he said a hand raise
assessment through wsib
um the recogition St remain the same if
inflamed um inject okay and it has not
and this was the the Sprint 12th of June
2017 okay please feel free to pause and
read thank you if you can but as I said
I was not examined on June 12th by this
doctor and he has so many notes eh so
many notes wow okay
as you can see new date June 6 the 12
June 12th 2017 and if INF flame ninj
okay I saw a different um radi uh radi
radiologist who was Monique Chris Chris
Taris okay ultrasound was done on the to
I went for the appointment on 26th of
July 2017 I went to get the cortisone
injection okay if he said so then you
know
um however the cortisol injection still
reveal as it says here that I still have
de andus can you see that here keeping
with
detis no fluid all right I still have
decantus but there was no fluid yet this
radiologist told me that she was still
going to in inject me with the cortisol
injection now the first um radi
radiologist in February did not inject
me with uh the in with the cortisone
injection however she explained why she
explained why I am not a dumb person I
have understanding if somebody explain
some things to me and it's clear I will
remember and she explained to me and
also the recogition says if there's
inflammation if there is and as per the
record radiograph radiologist in uh in
in in February she stated there was no
fluid it meant inflammation meant fluid
she said that the cortisone injection
needs fluid to be injected to for the in
for her to inject the um me with uh
cortisone injection right um anyway this
doctor decided that she was going to
inject me although is there were there
was no fluid there's supposed to be
fluid for me to get injected
so I ask her
why if there if there is no fluid why
she said Dr Jame Dr handles man told
her either told her to inject me on that
day I should still get the injection so
in other words in my opinion either
which way whether there's fluid or not
she should override the requisition then
that's this is my opinion she should
override the requisition and inject me
with the fluid inject me with the
injection although there was no fluid I
hope you're understanding me here to me
are they trying to hurt me to me if
there's no fluid they'll be causing more
hurt to me you understand they have no
regards for my health imagine there was
no fluid and the recogition said if
there is fluid inject if there's
inflammation inject that is it there was
no inflammation meaning there's no fluid
so I should not get the injection and
then I said doc doc with Dr Anders men
saying that I should get it there was no
medical reason for me to get it so I
told her no I said no so I said then I
started asking her about information
additional information on my uh on my
risk on my hand and stuff and she she
did not know so I asked her for MRI and
then she said I should ask my daughter
so here she she made matters worse for
me with man Life by saying the patient
was offered an injection she should not
have offered me the injection she should
not
into the first extensor compartment but
refused yeah I refused but I she should
not have asked me for me to refuse her
right she said until further
investigations of the risk are performed
yeah I did tell her why not do an MRI
one more thing I forgot to me mention
that after I saw Dr handers man on June
2017 sorry on June 12th 2017 and you
will see I've already pointed that out
to you
um um in in one of my other presentation
that I actually had to go to um another
clinic great leak Medical on that same
day because I did not get get any
answers from um Dr hesman right I went
to it and I had proof you have seen it
already Okay please feel free to pause
and read okay thank
you ref by the medical system and siib
but ability ignore my my injury placed
full I was placed back full time in my
regular position
okay okay this was when I was I just
brought this forward although it's
regarding manual life I was rejected by
dou Si I was denied a second time okay
um denied a second time because of bell
and because of the medical System
including manual life okay P fre PA and
re will get to that and when we get to
workplace safety and insurance board I
have a presentation on them also okay
please feel free to part and read if you
wish to do so now
thanks I also brought this forward
because workplace safety insurance Bo
and insurance board stated that my
doctor did not this is proof cuz I did
not know I'm no doctor so I did not know
right it said says here it is unusual
all right unusual so my doctor from day
one was doing me wrong that neither the
family doctor or the walkin clinic
physician the walk-in physician you see
the walkin physician referred me to my
doctor and told me to tell my supervisor
at the time that it was a matter for SIV
and also that my for my doctor I didn't
tell my doctor what that other doctor
said but the walkin clinic doctor was
not
my uh my treating physician you
understand thank I give great legs I say
thanks to great legs you know they had
enough evidences anyway on my injury
right but my doctor should be doing all
this right so it says the the the none
of these Physicians right provided a
form eight to the Ws to the Ws IB as
they are mandated by leg legislation
right and also that then PL I will I
will get to this part I will get to this
part here okay in my other presentation
but again just to show you the all the
system working together the form 8 all
right supposed to be provided all right
please fre you to pause and read I will
deal with it over on the wsib
presentation
okay here September 16th I went back to
Great Lakes great lak is a walking
Clinic my doctor you have to make an
appointment and sometimes when you make
the appointment the appointment is like
into like a week or two weeks so I
needed um immediate attention so I went
to the Great Lakes Medical on September
16th and then the doctor stated that I
should see a physiatrist open I'm
pronouncing that right right I should
tell my doctor to refer me right so I
went Dr James Chang's office eventually
got an appointment and I went and uh Dr
James Chang did not refer me to the
physiatrist as required by the walking
Clinic okay here I am uh this was
picture was taken on the 2nd of October
2017 and this was 7 months at work my
seventh month at work with injury forced
to work with left hand um okay which was
uh also in
pain
yeah oh my right hand is still in pain
and then my left hand became painful
too here Great Lakes Medical again in
pain um I was off work and because of
was off work I need the doctors's note I
would not have been able to get a an
appointment immediately so I went to
Great Lakes and on the September 13
2017 sorry October I'm trying to read
fast oh I'm saying the wrong thing so
sorry October 13 2017 right it's it says
that my medical reason was detis as you
can see okay I this was taken on the
15th of October 2017 okay this was a
Sunday at church
okay here am I at work all right face
fulltime full-time at work yeah um I see
I have the splint on see how big that is
my thumb spinker they would say thumb
spinker and I
um yes I I'm using my left
hand to type in an aggressive work
environment okay I only have I was 7
hours at my desk 250 minutes break and 7
hours at my desk okay 1 hour
lunch I I'm at
work and uh just letting you know that I
only had 250 minutes break and I work
from 8:30 to 5:00 okay 7 7 and 1/2
hours atw work praise yeah please feel
free to review thank
you off work again effective October
25th 2017 both hands were now in pain SE
is using right hand effective uh
September 7 2016 still soen and in pain
use um I've not used my right hand at
all since I was told don't use it in
2017 in September on September 7 2016
okay use left hand only since September
7 2016 to Pro to to present right um so
I've been using left hand over a year
compensating it for the right hand so
now it is in pain especially I was
placed again in that en aggressive
environment
okay on the
26th of October right this note as you
can see here I just let you know that it
was backdated because I was off work
again on the 25th of of um October and
the reason why the not was backed was
the 26th because I my appointment to see
my doctor when I was off I I was having
sleepless nights time and uh I was off
again and with both hands in pain so I
went Dr James Chang's office on October
31st and the not was back dated on back
to October 26 2017 reason because his
office not open on a Wednesday so he
could not have given me a note for the
Wednesday as I guess I guess it makes
sense he just backdated the no to the
26th I think he could have done it for
the 25th but you know it's just what it
is okay and um I my left hand I was
using Myan for over a year he in Dr
James T indicated both risk but I guess
I guess he forgot that it was my risk
and my left elbow my left hand really
was in pain anyway please feel free to
pause and read thank
you my life was forcing me back to work
with my in I was off work October 13 and
October 25th due to sleepless nights in
pain I was in pain every day every day
uh my life insurance did not approve did
not approve of my time of work right my
life insurance was aware of of a new
specialist appointment on November 17
2017 but was ignored my life insurance
misconstrued my conversations and
provided incorrect information to B
Mobility salary seized November 2017 no
benefits since um April 10 2017 unable
to attend physiotherapy unable to attend
phys therapy since um um physio since um
benefit sees April 10 can you imagine
yeah so I was left on my own to suffer
wow okay I received a letter from money
life after
um a conversation with them on November
10th and based off that I I was
displeased you know so I decided to
record and I have voice recorders um for
November 13 and November 16th however
this letter here um misconstrued my
conversation so I decided to keep uh to
cover myself actually my life insurance
SE salary effed November 1st for our
Force back to work um in my condition
benefits were already seized on April
10th therefore could not attend physio
they
stopped benefit so I could not attend
physio so I'm not in physio from April
and I had to wait until January 2018
okay and um and again I was not approved
by the bless IB so um pleas feel free to
read okay it's letter dated November 15
okay and it says here we have studied
the medical information that was
submitted to us including test results
symptoms treatments and your functional
capabilities as described by you and
your physician remember my Physician's
records whatever have been distorted you
know however it says um based on our
assessment we determine that you are not
eligible for short-term disability for
the following reasons based on our phone
call it wasn't October 10th it was
November 10th okay and the form that was
submitted by Dr James Jang right you
have confirmed that you do not have an
active and optimal treatment at this
moment I suggested on November 10th to
start physiotherapy treatment but you
refus treatment I could I start
Physiotherapy and I have to pay for
physiotherapy each session is $65 and
depends on depending on where I go some
are like $80 per session I got injured
at work and what this company man life
insurance who has been distorting my
medical records um coarsing the doctors
decided to tell me I have to pay out of
pocket right out of pocket for for
physiotherapy what audacity H okay to
have a voice recorder um
okay um it here it says as a result your
short-term disability benefits are
suspended retroactively November 1st if
you receive shter disability benefits
Beyond this that date necessary action
will be taken to recover those payments
please refuse to pause and read okay
thank
you
you you have contct
informationa for the individual
being please press to by name for
extension on the line if you know the
six digigit extension of the person
you're trying to
reach
please say the first and last name of
the person you would like to reach and
you will be connected you can also say
the name of the department you are
trying to reach or say directory for a
list of departments and toll-free
numbers if you need other assistance
please say
operator okay transfering you to three
Pro
hi good afternoon how are
you good good it's the l Grant
calling yes I the my well the doctor's
office confirmed that they F the
information Friday yeah so I'm just
wondering if you had re
it yes we
re yes I'm not sure what happened
there
e
and then I'm senen a specialist the
specialist on
Friday right so um they they did call me
also on Friday to confirm that it was
next Friday um I'll be seeing the The
Specialist so um I I I have to just wait
until he directs me otherwise so I don't
know what what I'm just waiting on what
he's going to
say okay all right now you don't have
any medication like
19 yeah because I have to see the
specialist cuz after see The Specialist
and you don't have any treatment at this
moment yes because I have to see the
specialist on the 31st the my doctor um
put a put a put something out that I
will see a specialist so when my
doctor's office called me now they told
me that the specialist appointment to be
on the 17th so I couldn't be at work now
because I am basically injured I can't I
can't perform at work so that's why I'm
off and I'm going just see the
specialist so there's nothing I can do
until I see the specialist so if the spe
I don't know do not know if the
specialist would be um what what
treatment or whatever I I have to wait
until I see a specialist I can't be
placed on medication when I don't know
what next you
know okay because right now like I do
last Friday and you would not be
eligible for the
shortterm because you don't have
anything any treatment so even if you
have received a 195 form you need to
have a treatment at this moment and
there's no reason why you should have
anything to help you to improve your
medical condition at this moment yeah
but but
but
end of part
two November 16
2017 don't have any
proof supp
without because just waiting
for so far you're waiting for the
injection so okay so so I should take it
then that to uh I will not be getting
any pay pay at all for this for this
paycheck that's what you're
saying okay all right I I'm not in
agreement but you know what it's as as I
I guess that's a policy I maybe that's a
new policy because I didn't uh I didn't
think
at the time and she was also requesting
for medical information and for
treatment
[Music]
yeah
maniz M screwed my um report and sent a
lie to B Mobility
okay as you realized from my previous
slide that money life insurance um
didn't want to wait at all they were
really anxious
in um taking away my salary and they
already took took away benefits in April
so they were really an they were really
anxious to ensure that um they would not
support me in the short-term disability
um regarding my injury right they're
saying I must be a medication on
treatment and all that however I told
them I'm seeing Dr silverberg no they
still went ahead head to stop my salary
okay so drct I saw Dr silverberg on
November 17th as you can see here right
um he did listen uh Dr silverberg took
time out to listen and he examined me so
he was thorough as I said there are
still good specialists around there are
still good doctors around just we just
have to find them okay um I'm not going
to say everyone it's just that the ones
I came across they did me wrong what you
know know with the exception of a few as
like for example Dr silverberg Dr
silverberg was thorough and uh he made
um when during examination he said as he
recorded here there was stress pain at
90° of abduction of the left shoulder
and terness of the left lateral
epicondilite risk dein tenosinovitis as
the result of V repetitive use of the
right hand at her job between May and
September 2016 and again in October 2017
and um Dr
silverberg um spoke to me about the the
cortis cortisol injection he told me
that it should have been administered
during the time the injury occurred I
would have had a better chance of
recovery but having it now for over a
year um um if I should get the Cod
having the injury for over a year if I
should receive the cordone injection it
will only provide temporary relief he
said it could be up to two weeks or less
it will not work you understand that's
what he explained to me right it was
then that doctor after Dr um silverberg
explained he then offered the injection
and I was wondering he just explained it
will not work so how come he's offering
it right then he said said no it's okay
it's your decision he told me about it
but it's my decision then I realized
that as a doctor he had to ask because
he told me it will not work and it's up
to me if I still want it for the
temporary relief all right if if he
should have gone to court and all that
for example he would be in trouble
because if he didn't offer me the
injection right couldn't make up my mind
for me right he would have to say well I
offered and she refused he could not
make up make up my mind by not offering
right so he did and I and I refuse and
here he mentioned we discussed a
cortisone injection notice the word
discussed all right and um he said we
discussed the Zone injection but she
chose to defer and it was a right thing
to do it was not going to work he said
even with a local cortisone injection
the patient would not in my opinion
um be a suitable candidate to return to
her previous vigorous keyboarding job
and then he said there is no specific
treatment for soft tissue injuries and I
do not anticipate Improvement in the
future um yes up to years later I still
have de of inin aitis I have to be
careful how I use my hand okay and um
here uh man life actually ignored doctor
silverberg's report man life was deemed
to ensure that um um whatever they do
was in favor of the mobility so Dr
silverberg's report how clear it was was
denied by man life insurance okay and
here I just want to bring a point out
that Dr silverberg did indicate there's
no family history of arthritis however
the Ministry of Health okay the Ministry
of Health here in Canada the record
stated that I have traumatic arthritis
okay please feel to please feel free to
pause and read and please stay with me
and listen in and uh on my journey here
in this country Canada okay I hope
you're not getting bored thank you for
your
time so updated I provide updates to WSB
lawyer and all that of what was going on
with the medical because doctors and
physiotherapists and man life insurance
and he actually told me that he did not
want to be involved in the medical
system at all you understand and um man
life was Mison screwing my my um my
report giving false report to B Mobility
on know my our conversation I do not
know if it's a language barrier between
French and English I don't know but the
thing is I told the lawyer that I did no
long I would no longer wish to converse
with man life insurance therefore you
agree to respond to the entity on my
behalf okay my benefits were in
reinstated in January 2018 so I'll go
over to the January 18
presentation okay please feel free to
bear with me please please feel free to
accompany me there okay thank you all
right